[
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$3\\frac{1}{2}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{7}{2}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$4\\frac{7}{3}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{19}{3}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$0{,}1$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{10}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$0{,}2$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{5}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$0{,}25$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{4}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$0{,}5$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{2}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$0{,}75$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{3}{4}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$0{,}125$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{8}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$0{,}2\\overline{3}$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{7}{30}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$0{,}23$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{23}{100}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$0{,}125$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{8}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$1{,}23$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{123}{100}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$2{,}5$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{5}{2}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$3{,}125$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{25}{8}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$7{,}2$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{36}{5}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$42{,}5$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{85}{2}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$42{,}50$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{85}{2}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$42{,}500$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{42500}{1000}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$0{,}04$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{1}{25}"
    },
    {
        "type": "open",
        "containerId": "zadania",
        "question": "Zamień na ułamek zwykły: $$5{,}125$$",
        "latexAnswer": "\\frac{41}{8}"
    }
]
